{
    "subject": "resource/Olympia_Snowe",
    "predicate": "property/birthname",
    "object": "Olympia Jean Bouchles",
    "human_readable": "Olympia Snowe's birth name is Olympia Jean Bouchles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9589036703109741,
            "question": "Is Olympia Snowe the same person as Olympia Jean Bouchles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9508505463600159,
            "question": "What was Olympia Snowe's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.932637095451355,
            "question": "What was Olympia Snowe's given name at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9224008917808533,
            "question": "When was Olympia Jean Bouchles born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9222312569618225,
            "question": "Where was Olympia Jean Bouchles born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8999437689781189,
            "question": "What is Olympia Jean Bouchles known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8589629530906677,
            "question": "Who is Olympia Snowe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8461624979972839,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Olympia Snowe and Olympia Jean Bouchles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678938865661621,
            "question": "Did Olympia Snowe change her name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4277627170085907,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Olympia Snowe?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Olympia Snowe's birth name is Olympia Jean Bouchles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1459_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Olympia Snowe change her name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1459_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Olympia Snowe and Olympia Jean Bouchles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1459_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Olympia Snowe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1459_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1459_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Olympia Snowe's birth name is Olympia Jean Bouchles.\" This can be seen in several of the documents, which mention that she was born Olympia Jean Bouchles."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}